http://nycdirectcremation.com/runtime.php?SiteId=254797&NavigatorId=1182144&op=privacy

Obituaries
Search
Use the form above to find your loved one. You can search using the name of your loved one, or any family name for current or past services entrusted to our firm.
Click here to view all obituaries
Search Obituaries
Immediate Need
We are here to help you. If you have need of our services, please call us, day or night, at:
(516) 223-3516
To better prepare yourself, we have provided you with some helpful information regarding the immediate need process.
Contact Us / Location
Metropolitan Funeral Service
Metropolitan Funeral Service
2283 Grand Ave.
BALDWIN, NY 11510
Phone: (516) 223-3516
Fax: (516) 223-9829
Email: michaelclfd@optonline.net
Home
Cremation Services
Our Cremation Prices
Ash Scattering Services
How to Decide on Cremation
What is Direct Cremation?
Cremation FAQ
Choosing a Cremation Provider
Unique Funerals on a Budget
Questions to Ask
Documents Needed When Someone Dies
Cremation Facts
The Cremation Process
Religious Views on Cremation
Planning Ahead
How Long Does It Take to Get Cremated After Death?
Will Your Wishes Be Honored?
Memorial Service Ideas & Checklist
How-To Section
How to Order Death Certificates
Writing an Obituary
Writing a Eulogy
How to Scatter Ashes
How to Deal with a Death
How to Tell Family Members
More
Obituaries & Tributes
It is not always possible to pay respects in person, so we hope that this small token will help.
Pre-Arrangement
A gift to your family, sparing them hard decisions at an emotional time.
Order Flowers
Offer a gift of comfort and beauty to a family suffering from loss.
No Hidden Fee Guarantee
We guarantee that the price we give you over the phone or you see on this site, will be the price that you will pay.
Privacy Policy
Metropolitan Funeral Service Privacy Policy
At, Metropolitan Funeral Service, we understand that the privacy of our visitors and the knowledge of our use of information collected from each visitor is important in our activities. Please feel free to read our privacy policy and we encourage you to contact our firm about any of the information located below if you need further assistance.
Contact Information:
If you feel that there is a need to contact our firm, please use one of the following methods:
Mail:
Metropolitan Funeral Service
2283 Grand Ave.
BALDWIN, NY, USA
11510
Phone:
(516) 223-3516
Email Address:
michaelclfd@optonline.net
Your IP address:
We collect the IP Address and Domain Name that is used when surfing our web site. We use this information for Site Traffic Statistics and analysis and only retain our last 60 visitors. We also receive your IP Address when you complete a search on our site inorder to help our firm better recognize what is being searched by our visitors. All IP Addresses and Domain Names are kept with the upmost confidentiality.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is used by Metropolitan Funeral Service only when there is persistent data that is required to use the Web Site, ie. Administration Mode, and when an E-Commerce order form is being completed. For general viewing of pages, there are no use of cookies.
When a user is wishing to purchase the product(s) that they have chosen they will be asked to complete a online form. When a user completes a section of the form and clicks on the "Next" button, not only does the form progress to the Next page but a cookie is created on the visitors computer with the information that they just completed. The purpose of the shopping basket cookie is to remember your information so that if you leave or get disconnected and come back to the order form our server will be able to complete the sections of the order form for you including product selected.
Security Monitoring
All login attempts to Administration Mode will be monitored by Metropolitan Funeral Service (CECERE). Each failed attempt is written back to the server and analyzed by the staff of Metropolitan Funeral Service (CECERE).
E-Commerce Module
Our E-Commerce Module incorporates the SSL technology provided by InternetSecure, a third party transaction company. When you are completing the ordering process the final step will take you from Metropolitan Funeral Service web site to InternetSecure 128-bit encrypted page. There your credit card information will be taken and the order will either be approved or declined. If your order is approved, Metropolitan Funeral Service receives only a confirmation number that your order was approved and a list of the items that has been ordered. The credit card information is not recorded either through Metropolitan Funeral Service or InternetSecure. If you have any questions please feel free to ask accounting@frontrunner360.com.
Questions & Comments
If you have questions, comments or concerns with either the way we use the information that is collected from your web browser or our privacy policy, please feel free to contact our firm.
Privacy Policy Template – AdWords Remarketing
This website uses Google AdWords
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Metropolitan Funeral Service (CECERE) website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
Facebook
Cremation Services
Our Cremation Prices
Ash Scattering Services
Veterans Cremation Services
Cremation Pre-Planning
About Us
Our Story
2283 Grand Ave.
BALDWIN,
